[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 03]
I want to challenge you.
Fine.
I'll wait for you to beg for my forgiveness.
Why didn’t you directly go to Senior Bai Feng
with the evidence?
You can give it to her and...
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Can you tell me your plan first
in the future?
She is the strongest among these female disciples.
Have you thought it through?
I...
Come down.
Fine.
Did I do something wrong?
Come to think of it,
you did nothing wrong.
Thank you.
The Lord is going to use the Moon Platform to contact Immortal Palace
to ask for the King Herb.
The King Herb gathered the spiritual energy of heaven and earth
and the essence of the sun and moon.
It can strengthen your body, prolong your life,
and enhance your vitality.
If we can get it,
it will surely solve my problem.
Wait for me outside.
Marquis Wuyang.
Why are you here
to see me?
I've encountered a bottleneck in cultivation.
May I ask
how can I get the King Herb?
King Herb?
You're still cultivating magic.
Yes.
Back then,
you knew cultivating the magic forcibly
will cost your life,
but you still insisted.
I know
what you did for the Three Realms
and the people.
But this is a serious matter
and there are many hidden dangers.
There's still no successor of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
As for the successor,
I will make the decision
before I die.
I just hope that in the remaining years,
I can use the power of the King Herb
to ensure peace in the human world.
Please enlighten me.
Spirit fire.
Only the destined person
who pass the test and training of the spirit fire
can get the King Herb in the Moon Washing Pond.
Thank you for your enlightening.
No one has passed the test and training of the spirit fire for so many years.
Can it really work?
There are Yin and Yang, but there are no strong or weak.
So Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
recruits both male and female disciples.
Today, all disciples will compete at the same time.
Best disciples will be selected among male and female disciples
and get promoted.
Male and female disciples will take part in the knockout
in two arenas separately.
The battle begins.
You can only use the weapon you chose.
You can't use any magic or spells.
Among these disciples,
there are several that are quite well-trained.
Xi, Lu Li, and Liu Shao
can be regarded as the best among them.
Lu Li.
Yes.
I noticed that you won easily.
You must still have energy.
How about
competing with Senior Du Mingchong?
For the final winner,
I...
I
will grant him a wish.
[Yu Yu Hall]
What are you waiting for?
You may begin.
Yes.
Brother, just beat him.
Liu Shao.
If nothing goes wrong,
even if Liu Shao can defeat other disciples,
she'll have to battle with Xi eventually.
Now the Lord gave me a chance.
If I want to protect Liu Shao,
I must
win this battle.
Show me what you've got.
Not bad.
Wang Jian.
Xu...Xu...
Xue?
Why are you here?
Where is Liu Shao?
She accepted the challenge for me.
I'm worried.
Liu Shao is not here.
Let me take you there.
Liu Shao!
Liu Shao.
Just an eye candy
with neither capability
nor cultivation.
How dare you speak for others?
How dare you dodge
my Silver Snake Whip?
Miss Xi.
It's all my fault.
Don't blame Liu Shao.
It has nothing to do with Liu Shao.
It's all my fault.
You're pleading for her?
How dare you!
The daughter of a lowly cook
is always a lowly person.
You deserve to be stepped on.
You want to change your fate
by entering Marquis Wuyang's Mansion?
Since your despicable father
doesn't care about your life,
I may just need to spend a little money.
How dare you team up with this eye candy
to block my way?
You want me to spare Liu Shao?
Fine.
Just break your arms.
Maybe I can spare her.
Why?
Liu Shao.
No.
Xue.
You don't have to do this.
This
has nothing to do with you.
-Liu Shao. -Xue.
You've never experienced hardships
and never suffered any humiliation.
You don't know about kindness.
You're different from us.
You don't know, do you?
People like you
are the most pathetic.
You want to teach me a lesson?
Who do you think you are?
Then I am determined to take
Xue's arms.
What is the sword intent of Lightning Slash?
I own this three-feet sword.
And I will use it to clear all injustices.
This is the sword intent of Lightning Slash.
For the superior Miss Liu
who spends money casually and
never knows the hardships of human,
it may be
too complicated.
I own this three-feet sword.
And I will use it to clear all injustices.
Your hands have been crippled.
People like you
don't deserve to be a disciple of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Lightning Slash?
Liu Shao!
-Liu Shao won! -She won!
-Liu Shao! -Liu Shao!
-Liu Shao. -Liu Shao.
Liu Shao.
Senior Bai Feng.
Am I mistaken?
It seems what Liu Shao used just now
is the Lord's Lightning Slash.
Du.
Senior Du.
Is your leg okay?
I just...
Go away.
This doesn't count.
We'll start over.
It is regulated that competitors can not leave the Tai-Chi Platform.
You lost.
Chong,
you are too careless.
This guy has always been cunning.
Let us start over.
Stop!
Chong,
admit your defeat.
But Lu Li,
if your senior had done his best,
you might not have won.
Yes. Yes.
There is no way I can defeat Senior Du.
Senior Du.
Thanks for letting me win.
My Lord,
you said
I could get a wish if I won.
Will you keep your promise?
Of course.
What kind of wish
do you want me to fulfill?
Any wish is fine?
Anything.
I, Lu Li,
want to...
My Lord.
My Lord,
we've got the winner of the female battle.
It's Junior Liu Shao.
Oh.
Really?
Liu Shao.
You won?
My Lord,
not only did I win,
I also performed the Lightning Slash.
I don't have to get smashed by you
like a golden leaf.
You won?
Well...
This year's disciples
are more interesting than before.
Lu Li,
you just said
what your wish is?
I...
I...I...
Wang Jian and I are like brothers.
Could you please make an exception and promote Wang Jian?
Who?
Me?
Come here. Hurry.
Kneel.
Hands.
You are loyal to your friends.
OK.
I agree.
-Thank you, My Lord. -Thank you, My Lord.
Liu Shao.
What about you?
Do you have any wish?
Please give Xue a chance.
With her ability,
she has surpassed many disciples in the mansion.
Come here.
Come on.
Really?
Okay.
I'm happy today.
All approved.
-Thank you, My Lord. -Thank you, My Lord.
However,
Liu Shao and Lu Li,
as the winners today,
you two
have to pass the test and training of spirit fire.
Spirit fire?
What is that?
Brother.
Your head...
That's enough.
All right.
Let go!
Let go of me!
-Cheers! -Cheers.
First, this drink
is for Xue and me.
We want to thank both of you.
Second,
it's for celebrating our promotion.
Fattie.
In order to thank us,
you took out all your money.
You kept saying
Liu Shao loves playing and eating.
Eat as much as you want tonight.
You don't have to prepare the banquet.
[Sword Washing Pavilion]
You two work so hard.
Even without our help,
you'll succeed sooner or later.
Well...
It's still thanks to
my brother's recommendation
that I can stay easily.
I'm more grateful to Liu Shao.
Thank you for letting me know
that I have my own value.
Later,
Lu Li and I have to attend
the test and training of spirit fire.
OK. Come on.
Let's have another drink.
-Cheers. -Cheers!
Cheers!
[Sword Washing Pavilion]
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Senior.
How are they doing?
Not bad.
Dismiss.
Thank you for your guidance.
Senior.
I didn't expect Master would let you sneak into Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
You have left for three years.
I'm here
hoping that one day
I can help you pull out the Moon Sword
and find out the mystery of your background.
Is this the legendary Moon Sword?
Yes.
For ten thousand years,
the legend says that
it can lead the human world to become powerful.
Ten thousand years ago?
That shouldn't
have something to do with my background.
Why must I be the one who bring it back?
Marquis Wuyang really hopes
someone can pull out
this sword with great power.
Watch out!
It's useless.
Only Marquis Wuyang,
the lord of human world, can open this Protection Spell.
It seems that
it's really a long way
to go to pull out the Moon Sword.
Don't worry.
I will help you take it away.
Later,
you will get the new uniform for disciples.
And it's time for you and Liu Shao
to go to the Forest of Spirit Fire.
I heard that
it is quite a strange place.
You must be careful.
Liu Shao.
Don't think the Protection Spell here can protect you forever.
I don't believe
you'll hide in the Marquis Wuyang's Mansion forever
and never come out.
[Yu Yu Hall]
What do you think? Look.
Is it pretty?
How is it different from before?
We are going to the Forest of Spirit fire,
not shopping.
It's the same whatever you wear.
Tell me if it's pretty first.
Actually...
Well...
Actually,
you also think it's pretty.
Right?
Let's go.
Actually, the eye candy looks pretty.
No.
How could she be an eye candy?
If she were an eye candy,
she would not master the Lightning Slash.
Ah!
What?
What's wrong?
Xi...
Ao Hen has been watching the Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Xi probably wanted to go home.
As soon as she left,
she got murdered.
I'm going back to report to the Lord.
Be careful.
Okay.
Although Xi went too far,
she didn't deserve to die.
Ao Hen causes chaos in the human world.
Is there anyone
that can control her?
It's fine.
If we train hard,
we can beat her sooner or later.
When I think of Ao Hen,
my hands will sweat.
Give me your hand.
Trust me.
I'm here.
Look.
I'm in your hands now.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I will protect you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Let's go.
[Forest of Spirit Fire]
My Lord.
They have entered the Forest of Spirit Fire.
I wonder if they
can bring me a surprise.
What?
This...
Is this the spirit fire?
Are you stupid?
These are just shadows of the spirit fire.
How could you see
the real spirit fire so easily?
Then how can we find it?
Watch out.
I've asked around.
Every time Marquis Wuyang's Mansion recruits new disciples,
they would arrange the best two
to get the spirit fire.
But after thousands of years,
no one can succeed.
The reason why the spirit fire is hard to get
is that it is a flame
left by the Sun Supreme God.
So it has the power of the sun.
The spirit fire
is one of the rare remains of Supreme Gods
in the Three Realms.
No one succeeded?
Is it because they couldn't find the spirit fire
or because they couldn't take it out?
It is said that the spirit fire
can devour people's memories.
Even if they have seen the spirit fire,
no one would remember it,
let alone successfully take the spirit fire out.
We can only try our best.
Let's go.
Don't walk so fast.
For thousands of years,
-the spirit fire enhances itself by devouring memories. -Follow up. Come on.
The Forest of Spirit Fire is therefore filled with fog.
I’m concerning that
if this goes on,
the whole forest will be swallowed by fog.
It's all an illusion.
What?
Are you leaving?
Yes.
I said there are only three days.
You give me the future.
I give you three days of happiness.
Liu Shao,
this is your choice.
Ten years have passed.
The fate has changed.
Do you regret it?
Regret?
I don't regret it.
I won't regret for my choice.
Liu Shao.
Wake up.
Who is speaking?
Liu Shao, wake up.
Liu Shao.
It's just a chirp of birds.
Why are you so scared?
But feathers in this color
are rare.
I think I was draged into a dream just now.
It must be it.
It woke me up.
What dream?
You just fell.
What happened?
In other words,
you've entered the fog.
Then it make sense why nothing happened to me.
Because I've been
looking for my past.
I don't have memory about things before my master took me in.
That's why I said the illusions here
are useless to me.
That's right.
It's not necessarily a bad thing to forget things.
The feather is beautiful.
In my whole life,
I've never seen
such a feather.
You're right.
I have to thank this bird.
Otherwise, if you forget about me,
I'll lose a lot.
That's right.
And that bird
is like the color of the sun.
Also,
that bird has three feet.
Isn't it amazing?
The sun?
What's wrong?
It’s said that the body of the Sun Supreme God
is a three-legged golden crow.
And the sun
is also transformed from the three-legged golden crow.
In that case,
this bird is...
Spirit fire!
Go after it!
They disappeared in the fog for two hours.
Looks like they're going to return in vain again.
Chong,
you were kicked out
after staying in the fog for merely half an hour.
But they can stay in there for so long.
I think
they might succeed.
Hush.
You're right.
That bird is really three-legged.
I know.
Liu Shao.
Go catch it.
Me?
The Sun Supreme God is a woman.
She doesn't like men getting close to her.
You should go.
She is ambitious. I like her.
Let me show you.
Wu.
Look, it’s wet and dark here.
I'm sure you can't eat or sleep well.
How about this?
Go back with me.
My family owns
plenty of fields.
Let me take you to enjoy great meals.
Besides,
I can build a pure gold nest for you.
What do you think?
Are you coming or not?
They did it.
Look.
I caught her so easily.
I must be really lucky today.
Hot!
They got it.
Let's go.
Come with me to help them.
You two stay here.
Liu Shao! Are you crazy?
It's so hot. Don't you know to let go?
Do you expect me to buy medicine for you?
Lu Li.
I found a secret.
What secret?
The more fiercely you treat me
means
the more
you care about me in heart.
Let me tell you.
I don't sell myself.
Don't try to cling onto me.
Isn't it hot with your hands holding it like this?
No.
How could it be hot?
I can block it with my vitality.
I can separate from its temperature.
But this is the spirit fire of the Sun Supreme God.
How can it be easily controlled?
You can get the golden crow easily.
Why can't I
control it?
Go out now.
Stop talking.
I don't want something else happens.
Get out.
Hurry up.
Take it.
Take it well.
Lu Li got the spirit fire.
I'm afraid the successor of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
will be him.
Senior Du,
those people are merely juniors who just entered the mansion.
They are just lucky.
How can they compare with Senior Du?
In my heart,
Senior Du is the best.
What’s wrong?
Why are you walking so slowly?
I...
I'm protecting you behind.
Come here.
What?
Show me your hand.
My hand?
What's there to see?
Look how badly you're injured.
Miss Liu.
Can you stop delaying?
I'm almost roasted pork trotters.
Can you hurry up?
Demon fire!
Watch out!
Lu Li!
My Lord.
What happened to Lu Li?
His meridian was burned
by the spirit fire.
I’m afraid his injury is troublesome.
How did the spirit fire hurt him?
I insisted on taking his spirit fire.
I thought I could reduce his burn.
But unexpectedly,
the moment I touched his hand,
the spirit fire exploded.
It’s all my fault.
It's all my fault.
Show me your hand.
Her  spiritual power is so strange.
It's against Lu Li's  spiritual power.
No wonder there was such an accident.
Although you two
successfully get the spirit fire,
Lu Li's injury is quite tricky.
If I want to cure him,
I'm afraid it will consume 80% of my vitality.
Now there are endless demons.
If the news of losing 80% of my vitality gets out,
I'm afraid
the human world will be doomed.
Then how to save Lu Li?
If she can get the spirit fire,
she might be able to get the King Herb.
It's fine.
It's not difficult for me
to cure him with the King Herb.
It's my fault.
Let me help you find the King Herb.
He did this
because he was afraid that I would get hurt.
No matter how hard it is,
I will find the King Herb
so that your vitality won't be damaged.
Why don't you ask
where
and how to get the King Herb
and is it dangerous?
As long as you can save Lu Li,
I'm not afraid of danger.
But...
Could you please not tell Lu Li about this?
He's badly injured.
I can't let him worry about me anymore.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Lu Li.
Get well soon.
You used to protect me.
Now,
it's my turn to protect you.
Even if I have to risk my life,
I'll get the King Herb back for you.
The demon hunting trial is about to begin.
During this period,
disciples can go in and out freely.
You can go to the Moon Washing Pond
to figure out the ways in this period
so as to find the King Herb as soon as possible.
Who's there?
Don't be afraid.
Although
I came here alone,
but the Lord has ordered the seniors
to clean the area.
It won't be dangerous.
Yes.
How to open the door
of the Moon Washing pond?
When you go to the entrance,
read the dirge.
Then there will be a way to the Moon Washing Pond.
The area with lanterns writen with "wu" hung over
is the safe zone.
The demons dare not come near.
The moon is bright.
The day is auspicious.
The water is waving.
The sun is shining.
May the four seas be safe.
Open!
Open...
Liu Shao.
I hope that Liu Shao can get the King Herb successfully.
This is not only about my life,
but also
the future of the human world.
[Wu]
[Moon Washing Pond]
Wow.
This place is so beautiful.
I must bring Lu Li here next time.
I should find the Moon Washing Stone first.
Right.
[Demon King in White He Na]
She's from Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Demon-driving Lantern?
Don't create more troubles.
Have a good sleep.
Who's playing the flute in the middle of the night?
How can she be not affected by my flute?
Is she...
I'm sure it came from around here.
Who's there?
Are you playing the flute?
I know you are a fish demon.
But don't worry.
Let me take you back to recuperate.
When you recover,
help me
find the King Herb.
Collect.
You may just rest here.
Sir Moss,
you are the elderly of the Demons.
You are knowledgeable.
Do you know
[Demonic Realm Sal Tree]
who can not be controlled by the Melody Flute?
Your Majesty,
the Melody Flute can disrupt people's mind
and bewitch people.
[Elder of the Aquatic Demons Sir Moss]
Person who will not be controlled,
other than the two Supreme Gods who have disappeared,
can only be Immortal Ze Shui
who has a deep grudge against us.
Your Majesty, do you want...
There is a woman in the mortal world
who is not afraid of the Melody Flute.
It must be her,
the heir of Immortal Ze Shui.
I've transformed a substitute on her.
Sir Moss, I hope I can find the answer this time.